

Koen Peters

Organisational, Strategy & Innovation Management

INFO



Name

Koen Peters



Adress

Jos Klijnenstraat 37 6412 HT Heerlen The Netherlands



Phone

+31 (6) 29271608



Email
Koen.Peters@live.nl



LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/khwpeters

SKILLS

German

English

Teamwork

Event Management

Critical Thinking

Presentation skills

REFERENCES

Available on request



PROFILE

As a recent International Business graduate, the pressure to 'know what to do with the rest of my life' becomes more real. Instead of pursuing a future in accounting, I realised that Strategic management and project based work captivates me much better. From September 2018 onwards, I'd love to start a master's degree in Innovation or Organisational Management, but for now I am gaining practical experiences.



Work Experience

2018 Heerlen Innovation Intern GroeiFabriek by APG

During my three months internship my assignment was assisting in various experiments concerning Blockchain, AI, Sustainability and the Sharing Economy. Brainstorming, research and helping with the day to day of 'would-be' start-

ups were my main tasks

2018 Heerlen **Innovation Intern**

Loyalis NV

During my three months internship my assignment was twofold; find a way to internalize outside-in innovation in the company culture and try to find an innovation externally that can be of value for Loyalis. Out of Interested, I also assisted the with revising the fraud detection strategy.

2016 -2017

Board Member – Event Manager (Activities Commissioner)

Maastricht SCOPE | 3MA

As a board member, together with my team, we were responsible for 40 volunteers, 100k revenues stream and 1200 members. As event manager I managed six teams hosting different recruitment events over the time of a year. I was also responsible for the HR/ Recruitment part of the organization.

2016

Controller Intern

Heerlen

Centraal Bureau voor de Statistiek

My primary task was supporting a local senior controller in her assignment of locating inefficiencies. Over the course of three months I got a lot of insight in how to make monthly reports, tracking down inefficiency and thinking outside of the box to

enhance sustainable working.

2012 - 2017

Various Jobs (student Jobs)



Education

2014 - 2018

BSc International Business (Major: Accounting)

Maastricht

University of Maastricht School of Business and Economics

GPA: 7,1/10

2017

BSc International Business (Exchange)

Newcastle

University of Newcastle (Australia)



Certificates

2016 **BHV/ ERO**

Maastricht NIBHV

2012 Elementary Bookkeeping

Heerlen In Balans

2012 – 2013 Cambridge Advanced English

Maastricht Cambridge